https://bannerart.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is Banner Art Studio’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://bannerart.com/, and other sites we own and operate.
We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.
We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.
Get a Quote Now(719) 657-2967info@bannerart.comFeatured Posts
WayFinding Signage for Zoos, Aquariums, Botanic Gardens
A picture’s worth a thousand words! Get people to your zoo, aquarium, museum or botanic garden exhibit...
New Art Installation: Atrium Hanging Art at Holloman AFB
We are so proud to reveal this colorful atrium hanging art installation commissioned by Holloman Air...
Choosing Thread for a Project
Banner Art Studio’s artistic process for choosing the components of our projects is part art, part...
In Progress in the Studio: Atrium Hanging Art for Holloman AFB
In progress now: Mettje and the team at Banner Art Studio are currently working on atrium hanging art...
Suspended Art Installations: Exterior Building Banners at Kidz Therapeze in Kileen, TX
Banner Art Studio was pleased to collaborate with Kidz Therapeze in Kileen, Texas to create this colorful...
